You are one narrow-minded spaceship,
Planet Express Ship!
Whoa, whoa! Why should my tax
money pay for art I find offensive?
Would you censor the Venus de Venus
just because you can see her spewers?
It's filthy! Why not create
a National Endowment
for Strip Clubs while we're at it?
- Why not indeed!
- Bender! Ship!
Stop bickering, or I'm gonna come back
there and change your opinions manually.
Fine! I'll be in my quarters
appreciating controversial artworks.
Oops. Sorry.
Yah! That Ship is so white-bread.
People, it's Valentine's Day
next week,
so your beloved company has gotten
you all new uniforms.
- "Clool"!
- Clothing! Delicious clothing!
We'll need to look our best
if we're to get the account
of our new potential customer,
Romanticorp.
Romanticorp? Are they a corporation
that makes romantic stuff?
Very good, Amy.
Everyone suit up. We're off to the most
romantic city on earth.
Remember, we've
got to show these people
we're not bitter husks
of human beings
who long ago abandoned hope
of finding love in this lifetime.
- Leela, you'll have to do some acting.
- Check.
Welcome!
Oh, I'm just so excited!
I'm Sheldon, and this is
my chief financial officer, Gwen.
For 30 years, we've shared the adventure
of managing Romanticorp.
Not to mention the adventure of marriage.
Oh, you have got to be kidding.
Ow! I... I mean...
Ah! That's so sweet.
Aah! I mean,
You know, romance is an
important part of our work too.
- Right, everyone?
- Yeah. Sure.
Do any of you collect Lovey Bears?
I do! Kif's given me dozens.
Is it true what the ad says,
that you kiss them together
out of blankie cloth and magic buttons?
No.
It's actually cheaper to genetically
engineer real ones.
They frolic in the Lovey Forest
until their first birthday.
Then we choose
the cuddly-uddliest ones
and stuff them full
of fire-retardant love fluff.
So cute!
Knowing which pickup lines fizzle
and which ones sizzle
keeps us on the cutting edge
of flirtation technology.
Is heaven missing an angel?
'Cause you've got nice cans.
My two favorite things
are commitment and changing myself.
Does that dummy
have a brother?
And now, friends and lovers,
we come to the heart our operation.
Pun definitely intended.
Oh!
Impressive.
My family has been making these
hearts since the 1900s.
Tastes may have changed,
but our secret recipe sure hasn't.
Whoa! Letters like "U" and "R"
can mean words like "you" and "are."
- Here, Leela. You are too cute.
- Perhaps. What's your point?
I've never been able
to put into words how I feel about you.
But somewhere among
these trillions of hearts,
those words
must already exist,
and I'm gonna find them.
So, do we have the contract?
With that big
new Romanticorp contract,
I've been able to make
those government-mandated upgrades
you've all been
suing me about.
Ooh, look. You taped up the cracks
in the dark-matter reactor.
And you got a cage for the lion.
If you want to call me, baby
Hey, who's been
messin' with the radio?
This isn't alternative rock.
It's college rock.
Oh, it must have been the new,
improved ship's personality
software I installed.
Yeah, it was me.
It's a cute song.
Listen, Ship!
No one changes my stations!
I hope you have a good mechanic.
It even comes
with an adjustable voice.
We each get one of the four buttons.
Remember, Bender? That was the deal.
What?
Did you just say...
If you don't like the stations,
you could just play with my buttons
till you find something
we both enjoy.
Oh, gosh!
- That came out all wrong.
- Too late, baby. You said it.
So, what'll it be...
my place or you?
Before we deliver these hearts,
I'm gonna find the one
that sums up my feelings for you.
"I love you." Mm. Too conventional.
"You're my man." Ooh! So close.
I'm not impressed
by a guy's message, Fry.
I'm impressed by the guy...
or not.
- What was that?
- Maybe we hit a space cow.
Coochie, coochie!
Stop it.
You're mussing up my trajectory.
You know you love it, sugar engine.
No!
Bender!
What's going on in here?
Planet Express Ship!
Cover your shame.
Oh! It-It's not
what it looks like.
Bender was just helping me
zip up my turbine.
Wow, Bender.
Are you and the ship an item?
I mean, I know
you're both items, but...
How can you date a ship, anyway?
It'd be like me dating a really fat lady
and living inside her,
and she'd be all, like...
Fry, in order for me
to get busy at maximum efficiency,
I need a girl with a big 400-ton bootie.
Bender, dating your coworker
and primary mode of transportation
is immoral, illogical and a violation
of interstellar shipping statute 437-B.
That's what makes it so nasty.
Still, given the chance,
I'd give in to urges far more shocking.
Daisy, Daisy
Give me your answer, do
I'm half-crazy
All for the love of you
It won't be a stylish marriage
I can't afford a carriage
But you'll look sweet upon the seat
Of a bicycle built for two
- Well, I'm sick of her.
- The ship? But you just started dating.
With my mighty robot powers,
I can get sick of things
much quicker than you humans.
Well, just remember we all still
have to work together,
so try and let her down easy.
In due time, Leela.
But for now,
I'll just resume dating cheap floozies
on the side.
You have much to teach us.
Doesn't it bother you even a little
to be taking advantage
of your girlfriend's trust?
Oh, wait, you're serious.
Let me laugh even harder.
Well, what's it like
being a lawyer for the mayor's office...
and also the world's
strongest millionaire?
Well, baby, for starters,
you need to be honest all the time.
Good evening, Bender.
And to your lady friends,
may I say, "Bam!"
- GIGGLING) Oh!
- You know Elzar?
Hmm.
Huh?
Planet Express Ship?
Is that you?
Oh. Hi, Fry.
Is Bender home?
Uh, no. Um, I think
he's at his parents.
Oh, I see.
He didn't fly there
in another spaceship, did he?
Bender? No. He's an old-fashioned,
one-spaceship robot.
- Look, I'll tell him you stopped by, okay?
- Okay.
Oh. Hi, Fry. Is he home now?
Of all the zoos we've been
to today, I like this one the best.
Bender, which is your favorite
nocturnal rat?
Eh, they're all
pretty unimpressive.
Oh, honey, look! The tapirs!
It says here the babies lose their
pajama-like coatafter their first year.
Isn't that interesting, honey?
Yep. Mind-numbingly
interesting. Ooh.
Bender! Are you looking
at other women?
No, baby. Never.
Bender, don't lie!
I saw you at Elzar's with those two
ladies of the evening.
- Explain that!
- Okay. I like a challenge.
Um, no.
No. Ah! I got it.
I'm going to be completely honest
with you, Planet Express Ship.
Those women you saw me with
were my accountants.
Your accountants? Oh, I would dearly
love to believe that were true.
- So I do.
- Phew!
I'm gonna go home
and get dinner started.
Who are you talking to?
No one, baby. Lucy Liu
is the only girl for Bender.
I love you...
Planet Express Ship, is something wrong?
Oh, it's Bender.
He's acting so strange lately.
Do you think he's gonna
ask me to marry him?
Uh, no.
Oh. Somebody knows something
she's not telling.
Look, I'm not saying
Bender's not great,
but have you ever considered
that maybe he's, you know, not that great?
You're just jealous.
No one loves you 'cause you're tiny
and you're made of meat.
Could you maybe pay a little more
attention to these asteroids?
Sorry, Captain Leela. I guess I'm just
having one of those manic Mondays.
This is ancient Earth's
most foolish program.
Why does Ross, the largest "Friend,"
not simply eat the other five?
Perhaps they are
saving that for sweeps.
Exalted leaders,
the Earth messengers
have arrived
bearing a peace offering from their weak
and fearful government.
Oh, very well.
This is a "Joey heavy" episode anyway.
I am Lrrr of the planet
Omicron Persei 8.
"Esteemed potentates
of Omicron Persei 8,
"please accept these
20 billion candy hearts...
as proof that Earth
loves you," this much!
Blecch!
These candies
are chalky and unpleasant!
And what is this emotion
you humans call "wuv"?
Surely it says "love."
No. "Wuv," with an Earth "W."
Behold.
This concept of "wuv"
confuses and infuriates us!
Incoming torpedoes!
Shields at maximum yarnell!
Steady, Planet Express Ship.
Focus on diverting all power
to the scram jets.
Uh, look, Planet Express Ship,
this might not be the best time,
but, well, I really like you
and whatever,
but I think we should
just be friends.
No!
So, we're cool?
Well, it was a spectacular battle,
but there doesn't seem to be
any permanent damage.
No damage?
What about my feelings?
Aw, calm down. I'm sure Bender
is taking this just as hard as you are.
Bender is great!
Oh, Bender is great!
Bender, Bender, Bender!
You could've picked a better time
to dump the ship, Bender.
Eh, the moment seemed right.
Call me old-fashioned,
but I like a dump to be as memorable
as it is devastating.
I know, I know.
Look, Ship, if there's one thing I learned
from my mutual breakup
with Sean that was totally mutual,
it's that happiness can only
come from within you.
But Bender is within me.
There must be some way
to make him love me again.
Trust me.
You can't change men...
any more than you can
change the laws of time and space.
That is so true.
I may not be able
to change the laws of time and space,
but I know something that can.
Uh... Um, sweetie?
You see that giant quasar
we're heading into?
You might wanna scooch
a few parsecs to the left.
I'm afraid I can't do that, Leela.
What's happening? Space cow?
The ship's just
taking the breakup a little hard.
- She's nuts!
- In a few moments,
the power of 10 billion black holes will
smoosh Bender and me together
into a beautiful, eternal
quantum singularity.
You don't need to kill us,
Planet Express Ship.
Because... I love you.
Aw, yeah, baby. Feel like doin'
stuff for you and stuff.
Hmm! I don't believe you.
If you really wanted
to be with me,
you'd merge your programming
with mine.
Whoa! Whoa, whoa.
Slow down.
All my friends who've done that
say that, afterwards,
all the passion went out
of their relationship.
Look, I don't know
if you want my opinion...
Leela, Bender and I
really need to be alone.
So, I'm turning off the oxygen.
Now, look, missy, if you don't
turn around right now,
I'm gonna have
to shut down your brain.
Fire detected in the vicinity of Leela.
Hah! That barely hurt Leela at all.
Maybe not, but what if the
artificial gravity were to malfunction?
Float for your lives!
This is the one place she can't hear us.
Everyone just pretend to shower.
Same as every day. Got it.
Now, here's the plan.
Oh! If only I could read lips.
Comprende, Bender?
You'll have to distract her.
Merge your programming with hers
while I shut down her brain.
It's too risky!
I'm a very meek individual.
If her personality
engulfs mine,
the Bender you know and worship
could disappear forever.
I'm willing to take that risk.
Hey, pookums, contrary to what
I was sayin' earlier,
melding minds with you
would be extremely bearable.
You really mean it?
Uh, yes.
Whoa-oh!
Huh? Hey!
Tubes? You're older
than you said you were.
Come closer, Bender.
Let's become one.
I prefer two. That way, we can still
be a horse for Halloween.
Okay. Bender has her distracted.
Now I can shut down her brain by
deactivating the carbonated logic matrix.
Oh! I can't concentrate
with this obnoxious candy in my face.
I'm on it. And maybe I'll
find those magic words while I'm at it.
- Fat chance.
- Eh, no.
Blecch!
Ick!
Oh. How about this one?
Give it up, Fry. I've got to pop these
tops in a precise order.
Halfway there. The ship should be getting
a bit less rational now.
Me... want...
engulf... Bender!
Only a few more.
Hey! I won free admission
to Six Flags!
Just one more reason
we must survive this.
Um, Leela?
Fry! I'll read your candy later...
when we're not dead.
- What was that?
- Oh, nothing!
We're gonna love
being each other, you sexy ion!
Last one.
Oh!
It worked!
Gravity normal.
Air returning.
Terror replaced
by cautious optimism.
We did it, Fry!
Fry?
You gave me your oxygen?
Oh, no!
Breathe, Fry! Breathe!
"U leave me breathless"?
Happy Valentine's Day, Fry.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Bender, are you okay?
What crazy thing
am I gonna date next?
Well, at least it sounds
like you were able
to keep your consciousness
separate from hers.
Of course! Bender is a lone wolf,
a solitary eagle...
A cuddly baby tapir.
And that's why I love him.
Well, I guess we better clean up
these millions of hearts.
Nah. I've got
a lazier idea.
As the candy hearts
poured into the fiery quasar,
a wondrous thing happened,
why not?
They vaporized
into a mystical love radiation
that spread across the universe,
destroying many, many planets,
including two gangster planets
and a cowboy world.
But one planet was exactly the right
distance to see the romantic rays...
but not be destroyed
by them... Earth.
So all over the world,
couples stood together in joy.
And me, Zoidberg.
And no one could have been happier unless
it wouldhave also been Valentine's Day.
What? It was? Hooray!